Come on 呼吸声也都是音乐般的stage (let’s go)
Come on Suara napas pun seolah musik Stage (let’s go)
Come on Even my breath is like music on stage (let’s go)
Come on 息づかいさえも音楽のような Stage (let’s go)
Come on Incluso la respiración se convierte en música en el Stage (let’s go)
Come on แม้แต่ลมหายใจก็เหมือนดั่งเสียงเพลงบน Stage (let’s go)
Bulir keringatku bagimu Heavy rain
我的汗水是你的Heavy rain
僕の汗のしずくは君にHeavy rain
Mis gotas de sudor para ti Heavy rain
เม็ดเหงื่อของฉัน สำหรับเธอคือ Heavy Rain
To you my sweat is heavy rain
Kapanpun Hot and shine
いつもHot and shine
Siempre Hot and shine
Hot and shine อยู่เสมอ
无论何时 Hot and shine
Always hot and shine
Di atas panggung Ride
บนเวที Ride
在舞台上Ride
ステージの上でRide
En la escena Ride
On stage ride
Matamu bereaksi lebih dulu daripada hati
君の目は心より先に反応する
ดวงตาของคุณตอบสนองเร็วกว่าหัวใจ
Your eyes react faster than your mind
Tus ojos reaccionan antes de tu corazón
你的眼睛比心先行
现在我们热情满溢
ตอนนี้เราเปี่ยมล้นไปด้วยความร้อนระอุ
Nos estamos hirviendo por el ardor
Sekarang kita dalam luapan kegembiraan
今僕たちは熱気にあふれてる
Now we’re overwhelmed with too much excitement
ゆっくり座って遊んであげる時間はない
没有时间放松陪你玩儿
Tak ada waktu tuk duduk nyaman bermain-main
No hay tiempo para estar sentados a jugar
I don’t have time to play sitting next to you
ไม่มีเวลาสำหรับการนั่งเล่น
過程を楽しんで僕と一緒にもっと走って
Disfruta del proceso Corre conmigo
Nikmati prosesnya dan larilah bersamaku
สนุกกับการวิ่งไปพร้อมกับฉัน
Enjoy the process run more with me
享受这过程 和我一起继续奔跑
もっと自由に望んでまた望んで
Ingin lebih bebas lagi dan lagi
ฉันต้องการอิสระมากขึ้นและมากขึ้นอีก
Libremente, desea y desea
更自由地去渴望 去追求
More freely want more and more
Too lit too litty we rolling
僕は君の夢でありながら夢にまで届く通り道になる
我是你的梦想
Soy tu sueño
Aku adalah mimpimu
ฉันคือความฝันของคุณ
I become your dream and a path to it
Y al mismo tiempo el camino al sueño
也会成为你到达梦想的通道
Dan jalan menuju mimpimu
เป็นเส้นทางสู่ความฝัน
君の夢をつかませてあげられるさ Oh
Mimpimu
Tus sueños
ความฝันของคุณ
让你将梦想握在自己手中 Oh
I can make you hold your dream Oh
Dapat kutangkap dalam genggaman Oh
Te los puedo traer a los manos Oh
ฉันสามารถนำมันมาไว้ในมือของเธอ Oh
Dengan wajah polos
純粋な表情で踊っていた子供は今笑いながら
曾经一脸天真
The dancing child with an innocent face
El niño que bailaba
สีหน้าที่ไร้เดียงสา
Con cara inocente ahora sonríe
跳着舞的孩子 现在正笑着
Anak yang dulu menari kini tersenyum
ของเด็กที่เต้นอยู่กำลังยิ้ม
now smiles and sets this track on fire Oh
このトラックに火をつける Oh
点燃这段Track Oh
Membakar track ini Oh
Y prende fuego en la pista Oh
และจุดไฟให้กับแทร็คนี้ Oh
We got that
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
Yea We got that We like that
把我投入其中
Throw myself and wake you up
Me tiro
僕を飛び込んで君を目ざまさせて
Lempar aku
โยนฉันขึ้นไป
Y te despierto
และปลุกเธอขึ้นมา
Bangunkan dirimu
将你唤醒
Show me what you got
El resultado Crazy
The outcome is crazy
結果はクレージー
Hasilnya Crazy
ผลลัพธ์ที่ได้คือ Crazy
最终是Crazy
Como tu corazón que palpita
เหมือนกับเสียงเต้นของหัวใ
随着心跳
Just like your heart runs
胸が響くままに
Seirama detakan jantung
走しろうぜRight now
Corre Right now
ลองวิ่งไป Right now
狂奔 Right now
Run Right now
Larilah Right now
Yea skip เป็นคำที่ไม่เหมาะกับฉัน
Yea skipは僕に合わない単語
Yea skip是不符合我的词汇
Yea skip no es la palabra correcta para mi
Yea skip kata yang tak cocok untukku
Yea skip is not the right word for me
ฉันอยากเป็น Winner ในทุก Story
Quiero ser de toda Story el Winner
我想成为所有故事中的胜者
I want to be the winner in every story
Kuingin jadi semua Story Winner
僕はなりたいすべてのストーリーのウイーナー
El miedo Zero
ความกลัวเท่ากับ Zero
恐惧是Zero
恐れはゼロ
With zero fear
Rasa takut Zero
Ahora al revés
现在正相反
Now on the contrary
今逆に
ในตอนนี้ ตรงกันข้าม
Sekarang sebaliknya
อัตราการเต้นหัวใจ 100 กิโลเมตรต่อชั่วโมง
心潮澎湃 时速时速100公里
Detak jantung per jam per jam 100kilo
ときめく心臓時速時速100キロ
My fluttering heart at 100 km/h
Mi corazón late a 100 km por hora hora
Aku adalah semua cahaya VIP
僕は すべての明かりのVIP
ฉันเป็น VIP ของแสงสว่างทั้งหมด
I’m the VIP of all lights
Soy el VIP de toda iluminación
我是所有灯光的VIP
待ったことはNo　待たせるのさ
Tak pernah menunggu No Yang ditunggu
从来不等待 只令人期待
No espero, Hago que me esperen
I’ve never waited No I make them wait
ฉันไม่เคยต้องรอ No มีแต่ทำให้รอ
覚えておけどこでも僕の僕のビート
Ingatlah di manapun milikku milikku Beat
No te olvides en cualquier lugar de mí mí Beat
要记住 无论何处 我的节拍
Remember anywhere my my beat
จำเอาไว้ไม่ว่าที่ไหน Beat ของฉัน ของฉัน
溶けるはずさ 君の心はアイスクリーム
你的心融化就像 Ice cream
Meleleh hatimu Ice cream
Tu corazón derretirá Ice cream
หัวใจของคุณจะต้องละลายเป็น Ice Cream
Your heart will melt
Ice cream
Sekarang kita wujudkan mimpi Player
今僕たちはその夢を叶えた Player
Somos los que han vuelto sueños en realidad, Player
Now we are the Player who made the dream come true
ตอนนี้พวกเราคือคนทำให้ฝันเป็นจริง Player
如今我们是实现梦想的Player
僕の中の僕は僕への賛辞を叫ぶ
Me inside myself shout praises to me
Dalam hati teriakkan pujian tuk diri
Yo dentro de mí grita elogios hacia mí
内心的自我 向我大呼赞词
ข้างในฉันส่งเสียงร้องชมเชย
The thrill of every second Danger
La emoción de cada segundo Danger
一分一秒都感受到战栗Danger
Tiap menit dan detik terasa getaran Danger
一分一秒が感じられる鳴り Danger
รู้สึกถึงความตื่นเต้นทุกนาทีและวินาทีที่ผ่านมา Danger
我渴望更刺激的激动
Kuingin debaran lebih kuat
ฉันต้องการความตื่นเต้นที่ร้อนแรงมากขึ้น
Quiero un temblor más fuerte
I want a stronger thrill
もっと刺激的な響きを僕は望むさ
我们要去往更高 We rolling
Vamos más arriba we rolling
เรากำลังไปสูงขึ้น we rolling
Higher we rolling
Semakin tinggi we rolling
僕たちはもっと高く We rolling
我是你的梦想
Soy tu sueño
僕は君の夢でありながら夢にまで届く通り道になる
ฉันคือความฝันของคุณ
I become your dream and a path to it
Aku adalah mimpimu
也会成为你到达梦想的通道
เป็นเส้นทางสู่ความฝัน
Y al mismo tiempo el camino al sueño
Dan jalan menuju mimpimu
让你将梦想握在自己手中 Oh
Tus sueños
ความฝันของคุณ
I can make you hold your dream Oh
君の夢をつかませてあげられるさ Oh
Mimpimu
ฉันสามารถนำมันมาไว้ในมือของเธอ Oh
Te los puedo traer a los manos Oh
Dapat kutangkap dalam genggaman Oh
สีหน้าที่ไร้เดียงสา
Con la cara inocente
純粋な表情で踊っていた子供は今笑いながら
曾经一脸天真
Dengan wajah polos
The dancing child with an innocent face
El niño que baila ahora sonríe
Anak yang dulu menari kini tersenyum
跳着舞的孩子 现在正笑着
ของเด็กที่เต้นอยู่กำลังยิ้ม
now smiles and burn inside your heart Oh
Arde dentro de tu corazón
แล้วให้ลุกไหม้ในหัวใจของคุณ Oh
Membakar hatimu Oh
点燃你的心中 Oh
君の心臓に火をつける Oh
We got that
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
Yea We got that We like that
僕を飛び込んで君を目ざまさせて
โยนฉันขึ้นไป
Me tiro
Throw myself and wake you up
Lempar aku
把我投入其中
และปลุกเธอขึ้นมา
Y te despierto
将你唤醒
Bangunkan dirimu
Show me what you got
最终是Crazy
ผลลัพธ์ที่ได้คือ Crazy
結果はクレージー
The outcome is crazy
El resultado Crazy
Hasilnya Crazy
เหมือนกับเสียงเต้นของหัวใ
随着心跳
Seirama detakan jantung
胸が響くままに
Just like your heart runs
Como tu corazón que palpita
走しろうぜRight now
狂奔 Right now
Larilah Right now
Corre Right now
ลองวิ่งไป Right now
Run Right now
こんなにも
如此
Inilah
This much
ดังนี้
Todo esto
充满自信的眼神 你也知道
確信に満ちた目つき君も分かるさ
Pandangan penuh percaya diri kau pun tahu
La mirada convencida tú lo sabes
สายตาที่เต็มเปี่ยมไปด้วยความมั่นใจขนาดนี้ เธอก็รู้
Confident eyes you know that
全部やり遂げられる僕たちは
We can handle all of them
Semuanya pasti bisa kita atasi
Nosotros no podemos manejarlo
เราสามารถควบคุมมันได้
我们能承受全部
僕の夢は現実になって今僕は
我的梦想已成真 此时我
Mi sueño se hizo realidad y ahora
ความฝันของฉันเป็นจริง และตอนนี้ฉันก็เป็น
My dream is now reality
Mimpiku telah jadi nyata kini ku
Now I freely fly
自由に Fly
自由地Fly
Dengan bebas Fly
อิสระ Fly
Libremente Fly
僕は君の夢でありながら夢にまで届く通り道になる
我是你的梦想
ฉันคือความฝันของคุณ
Soy tu sueño
Aku adalah mimpimu
I become your dream and a path to it
Y al mismo tiempo el camino al sueño
也会成为你到达梦想的通道
เป็นเส้นทางสู่ความฝัน
Dan jalan menuju mimpimu
让你将梦想握在自己手中 Oh
君の夢をつかませてあげられるさ Oh
Tus sueños
ความฝันของคุณ
I can make you hold your dream Oh
Mimpimu
Te los puedo traer a los manos Oh
Dapat kutangkap dalam genggaman Oh
ฉันสามารถนำมันมาไว้ในมือของเธอ Oh
純粋な声で歌っていた子供は今笑いながら
El niño que cantaba
Dengan suara polos
ด้วยน้ำเสียงบริสุทธิ์
The singing child with an innocent voice
曾用纯净的声音
ตอนนี้เด็กที่ร้องเพลงกำลังหัวเราะ
唱着歌的孩子 现在正笑着
Con voz inocente, ahora sonriendo
Anak yang menyanyi kini tersenyum
now smiles and attracts you into this track Oh
Membawamu ke track ini Oh
Te guía hacia la pista Oh
引领你来到这段Track Oh
このトラックへ君を招く Oh
นำพาเธอไปตามแทร็คนี้ Oh
We got that
Boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom
Yea We got that We like that
โยนฉันขึ้นไป
Me tiro
Lempar aku
把我投入其中
僕を飛び込んで君を目ざまさせて
Throw myself and wake you up
Y te despierto
และปลุกเธอขึ้นมา
将你唤醒
Bangunkan dirimu
Show me what you got
ผลลัพธ์ที่ได้คือ Crazy
El resultado Crazy
Hasilnya Crazy
最终是Crazy
結果はクレージー
The outcome is crazy
เหมือนกับเสียงเต้นของหัวใ
Como tu corazón que palpita
随着心跳
Seirama detakan jantung
Just like your heart runs
胸が響くままに
Larilah Right now
Run Right now
走しろうぜRight now
Corre Right now
ลองวิ่งไป Right now
狂奔 Right now